[{"answer": "I truly don't think about it.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "But to be serious, and I hope the answer is yes because it gives me some succor in this relationship we now have, is being so cool itself a terrible burden?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "OK, OK, I'll buy that one.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "How could she not be given the product of her parents, two of the coolest people?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Coolness runs in the genes, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "What would make you cool is the fact that you don't try.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "How do you effortlessly, without any effort, get to be cool?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "That's what's -- that's what's wonderful about people.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "I'm trying too hard?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Your mom, from what I've gleaned, a softer character?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I was 21.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "I mean how old were you when that happened?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It had a very deep effect on me.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What effect did it have on you?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "With me in her arms, like ringing the bell.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Which always reminds me that scene from \"Goodfellas.\"", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "With you in her arms?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "To you?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "An emotional barrier?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "I think he -- I think he honestly had a spiritual awakening because he -- you know, and I don't want to paint him as this, you know, horrible man.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "So when you had this time with him, when he knew he was dying, do you think because he realized he wasn't going to be around, this was the last chance to have that conversation with you?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "He made mistakes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "What did he say to you when he finally opened up?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "And you know -- no, she wasn't.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Was your mother still alive?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "-- amazing time with your father?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Wonderful.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "How would she felt about that, do you think?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "And she was in real life.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "What are the chances of that, right?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Most definitely.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Did they try and protest about it?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes, but harmless.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Did you get picked on at all once the TV show took off?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Well, it's funny because I -- you know, I've been in Europe touring a lot touring lately.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I don't know him.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Do you know Obama?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "So that was right?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "It wasn't Michelle, was it?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "And what is that, Piers?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Don't try and be too modest.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "How do I feel?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, to treat them with respect and so forth.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What did your mother tell you about women and how to treat them?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I would -- I would like it to change.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Have you got anyone?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I just love women.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What is it you love about women?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Because you seem so effortlessly charming.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Am I easy to be with?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Completely.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "I mean do you -- does that concern you?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Twenty-one.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Twenty-one?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "It put something in me.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "What did it do, do you think?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Was there a moment for you when you did something and you thought, my father was right?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "People are people.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Famous sex symbols?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "But do you dream, you know, wistfully of getting married, having more children, that kind of conventional thing?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": ": Young.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "But what went wrong there?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Young.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Too young?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I'm not concerned at all.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Are you happy or are you concerned?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "No, it's not easy.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "It's not easy, is it?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "As my mother said, self-praise is no recommendation.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Are you a good dad, do you think?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "You'll have to ask her.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "I'll pin Zoe down and said how goofy does your dad get?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Eleven.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Your family came to Hollywood when you were how old?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I remember the first day it was quite strange.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "What was it like for you?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "So many.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Who are the most naturally gifted artists you've encountered in your lifetime?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "You can't really name it.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "It's just that thing, something special.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Can you describe it?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I don't know if I've ever come to that point.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What was the moment for you?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I'm -- somehow I'm always still that kid who was trying to get the record deal.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "You don't think you're a star?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I think I put myself up -- I put myself up against the greatest people, these people that I mentioned, these people that influenced me that are amazing.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Is that insecurity or is it hard work?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "He was very much like he is now.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What was he like?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Who has more tattoos?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Not actually, the words.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "You have a whopping Jesus Christ on your back, right?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "How many have you got?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Not all of them.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Have you?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "So who has taken more drugs, you or Slash?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I suppose at the time I thought it was.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Is it -- is the drugs process that so many musicians go through, is it tangibly better for creative music making?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "All day long.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "All day long?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Well, it just basically puts this wall of fuzz around you.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "And what does that do to you over time?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, yeah.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Are you pretty clean these days?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Do you ever go recklessly partying?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "I have some stuff.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What have you got in there?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Any Litore (ph)?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "'61?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "Wow, really?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "That was a beautiful experience.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "A very powerful movie that, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "The career moment.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "But what's the career moment where if you had the chance, you'd relive it?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Being -- probably producing Michael Jackson.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "What was the biggest pinch?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Well, the fact that, you know, I wouldn't be here today if I hadn't seen the Jackson Five when I was six years old.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "What made it so extraordinary?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "RAVITZ: Of course.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "Do you think of our lifetime, Michael Jackson was the best?", "qSentId": 792}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 796, "question": "The greatest naturally gifted, as you said earlier?", "qSentId": 795}, {"answer": "Yes, completely.", "docId": "111221pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Entertainer of them all?", "qSentId": 797}]